到目前为止大概是这样子…
This is pretty much what's happened so far.
打从一开始罗斯就爱瑞秋
Ross was in love with Rachel since forever.
但每次他想要表白 总是会遇上阻碍…
Every time he tried to tell her,something got in the way...
像是猫米，意大利家伙
...Iike cats,Italian guys.
最后钱德劝他死心
And finally,Chandler was,like,"Forget about her."
罗斯去中国考古时 钱德说漏嘴罗斯爱瑞秋
When Ross was in China,Chandler let it slip that Ross loved Rachel.
瑞秋非常惊讶
She was,like,"Oh,my God!"
于是她到机场接罗斯
So she went to the airport to meet him.
她不知道罗斯 带了另一个女人下飞机
She didn 't know Ross was getting off the plane with another woman.
你们需要知道的大概就是这样子了
That's pretty much everything you need to know.
说够了我们，你们近来如何？
But enough about us. How have you been?
六人行 第2季 第01集 罗斯的新女友
The One With Ross' New Girlfriend
从北京飞来的第457号班机 已经降落
Flight number 457 from Beijing now arriving.
我的天啊！
Oh,my God!
天啊！
对不起
Excuse me.
借过，借过！ 紧急事件，拜托！
Move,move,move! Emergency,please!
对不起，对不起
Excuse me,excuse me.
原来你们在那里！
There you are!
那么，那么…
So,so....
中国怎么样？老兄！
How was China? You!
很棒…
It was great.
你怎么啦？
What happened?
你在流血 是吗？
-You're bleeding. -I am?
啊，天呐！我是在流血
Oh,look at that! Yes,I am.
别管我了 来自东方的归来先生！
Enough about me,Mr. Back From The Orient!
我要听一切事情！ 什么都不要漏掉！
Come on,I wanna hear everything! Everything!
嗯，要从何开始？
Well,where do I start?
这位是茱莉 茱莉，这位是瑞秋
This is Julie. Julie,this is Rachel.
这些…
These are....
These are...
…不是要给你的
...aren't for you.
这些是要送给你的
These are for you.
欢迎光临我国
Welcome to our country.
谢谢，我是纽约人
Thank you. I'm from New York.
没关系，我用它来止血
No problem. We'll use them to stop the bleeding.
去拿行李？
Baggage claim?
她去了机场 准备跟罗斯继续发展了
She went to the airport,and she's gonna go for it with Ross.
天啊！这是大事！
Oh,my God! This is huge!
这比大事还大 这是…
This is bigger than huge. This is....
什么比大事还大？
All right,what's bigger than huge?
这件事吗？
This?
喂，你们剪头发了！
Guys,you got new haircuts!
是的，谢谢维达布菲（维达沙宣是国际美发大师）
Yes,we did. Thanks to Vidal Buffay.
我们的光彩来自你的风采（沙宣广告词）
Because,you know,"lf you don't look good,we don't look good."
我喜欢这声音！
I love that voice!
各位!胜利者是艾娃.高的纳！
And the winner is Eva Godna!
各位！
You guys!
机场…机场…罗斯
Airport. Airport. Ross.
不是一个人
Not alone.
茱莉
Julie.
搂着她！
Arm around her!
抽筋！抽筋！
Cramp! Cramp! Cramp!
她好像想说什么
I think she's trying to tell us something.
赶快猜动词
Quick,get the verbs.
你！你！
You! You!
你说他喜欢我！
You said he liked me!
你！
You!
你们太慢了！
You slowpokes!
是的，我们拿了行李
That's all right. We got the bags.
这是我妹妹莫妮卡
This is my sister,Monica.
这是钱德
This is Chandler.
菲比，嗨
Phoebe,hi.
乔伊
Joey.
各位，这位是茱莉
Everyone,this is Julie.
茱莉
Julie.
但我还没到 我们还没见面
But I'm not here,you haven't met me.
没有连坐二十小时飞机  我会看起来更好一些
I'll make a better impression when I don't have 20 hours of plane on me.
还有巴士 喔，天啊！
-And bus. -Oh,my God!
那个尖叫的家伙… 还有吐口水
-With the screaming guy -And the spitting.
你们一定要听这个故事
You gotta hear this story.
我们坐的巴士一定有两百年旧
We're on this bus that's 200 years old.
至少两百年旧
Two hundred,at least.
一只鸡拉屎在她腿上！
And the chicken poops in her lap!
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我说出了结尾，对不对？
I just gave away the ending,didn't l?
我在计程车上听了这个故事…
I just heard this story in the cab...
…满脑子想的都是这个
...and it is all I can think about.
真是惊人
This is amazing.
怎么发生的？
How did this happen?
罗斯与我一起上过研究所
We were in grad school together.
后来就没有再见面 我降落在中国机场时…
We haven't seen each other since then. I land in China...
…猜猜是谁负责探勘？
...guess who's in charge of the dig?
就是茱莉！
Julie!
真是太棒了！
Isn't that great?
是不是像踢你的裤裆和朝你的脖子吐口水一样神奇？
Isn't that just kick-you-in-the-crotch,spit-on-your-neck fantastic?
她习惯这么说
It's an expression.
我们只是来打个招呼
We just wanted to say a quick hi.
然后我们要去看宝宝 然后睡一下觉
-Then we'll see the baby. -Then get some sleep.
现在是中国的明天晚上六点
It's 6:00 tomorrow night,our time.
别告诉我未来会发生什么事 我比较喜欢惊喜
Don't tell us what's gonna happen. I like being surprised.
再见！
Bye!
中央公园咖啡店
瑞秋，我想喝点咖啡 没问题
-Can I get some coffee? -Sure.
你跟他谈了吗？ 没有
-Did you talk to him yet? -No.
没咖啡给你
Then,no.
你在中国发生了什么事？
What the hell happened to you in China?
你离开前还疯狂爱着… 你知道的
When last we left you,you were in love with,you know.
我知道我爱她
I know I was.
但我心中有这个小声音告诉我
But there was always this voice inside that kept saying:
不可能成功的，死心吧 你知道那是谁的声音吗？
"It's never gonna happen. Move on." You know whose voice that was?
上帝？
God?
是你的声音，老哥
It was you,pal.
也许是上帝模仿我的声音
Maybe it was God doing me.
来自上帝的旁白，在模仿声音方面他是个天才
Aside from being almighty,he's a wiz at doing voices.
你说得对 她眼中只把我当成朋友
You were right. She looks at me and sees a friend. That's all.
然后我遇见了茱莉
And then I met Julie...
我们在一起非常开心
...and we're having a great time.
要不是因为你 我绝不会跟茱莉在一起
I never would have gone for it,if it hadn't been for you.
你欠我一个情，大个儿
Well,you owe me one,big guy.
你的柠檬汁
Your lemonade.
我没有叫柠檬汁
I didn't order it.
那你最好送回去 否则他们会要你付钱！
Then go take that back. They'll charge you for that.
快！快！快去！
Go,go,go! Come on,come on!
你问出了什么？
So what did you find out?
他说…
He said....
他们在一起很开心
They're having a great time.
对不起
I'm sorry.
但有一线希望 如果你愿意这么看…
But the silver lining,if you wanna see it...
他完全是自己做了这个决定
...is that he made this decision all by himself...
完全没有受外人的影响
...without any outside help whatsoever.
这怎么是一线希望？
How is that a silver lining?
你要非常愿意才看得出来
You have to really wanna see it.
讽刺的是这些家伙 上体育课时没人愿意跟他一队
Ironically,these guys were picked last in gym.
菲比
Hey,Pheebs.
你知道我想什么吗？
You know what I'm thinking?
因为…
How...
你太久没做爱了…
...it's been so long since you've had sex...
你不知道有没有什么改变？
...you're wondering if they've changed it?
一点儿都没猜对？
Not even close?
没有 但是我现在是这么想了
No. Although now that's what I'm thinking.
你本来在想什么？
So what were you thinking?
你帮他们剪头发 我想你也应该帮我剪
You gave the guys great haircuts. I thought you'd like to do mine.
不要
No.
为什么不要？
Why not?
因为我是个…
Because I'm just....
我非常挑剔 而且有控制狂
I'm incredibly anal and an unbelievable control freak.
不，你才不是
No,you're not.
我知道我不是 不过你是
I know I'm not,but you are.
我只是不想伤害你的心
I was trying to spare your feelings.
请等一下
Hold on.
罗斯，茱莉找你
Ross,Julie for you.
打扰一下，谁给了她我们的电话号码？
Excuse me.Who gave her our phone number?
好吧，那么，谁有动机？
Okay, well....Who had the motive?
是那个演员吗？
Was it the actor?
这个厨师？这个按摩师？
The chef? The masseuse?
或者是那个跟她约会的人？
Or was it the guy who's dating her?
是那个跟她约会的人
Guy who's dating her.
谁能介绍一个好裁缝？
Anybody know a good tailor?
需要改衣服吗？
You need clothes altered?
不，我只是要找一个人 用粉笔在我身上画线
No,I'm just looking for a man to draw on me with chalk.
去找法兰基 我家人都找他做衣服
Go see Frankie. My family's been going to him forever.
我十五岁第一套西装 就是他做的
He did my first suit when I was 1 5.
不，十六岁
No,wait,1 6.
不，对不起，是十五岁
No,excuse me,1 5.
1990年是几岁？
All right,when was 1 990?
当你用棉花签掏耳朵时 碰到东西就要停下来！
You have to stop the Q-Tip when there's resistance!
亲爱的，待会见
Sweetheart,I'll see you later.
好，再见
Okay,bye.
你真好
That is so sweet.
好，不，你先挂
Okay. No,you hang up.
不，你先…
No,you
一，二，三
One,two,three.
你也没有挂
You didn't hang up either.
她没挂
She didn't hang up.
不，你挂电话
No,you hang up.
你挂，你挂
You. You.
对不起，我以为你在跟我说话
Sorry,I thought you were talking to me.
瑞秋！
Rachel.
我打回去
I'll just call her back.
嗨，亲爱的，对不起 我们被中断了
Hi,sweetie. I'm sorry. We got disconnected.
不，你挂掉
No,you hang up.
我到底是怎么回事？
How did this happen to me?
一周前，两周前，我很好
A week ago,two weeks ago,I was fine.
罗斯只是罗斯 只是这个家伙
Ross was just Ross. Just this guy.
现在突然间，他不一样了
Now all of a sudden,he's Ross...
变成这么好的男人 我却无法得到
...this really great guy that I can't have.
亲爱的，我也希望你能得到他
Sweetie,I wanted you to have him too.
我知道你的心意
I know you did.
嘿，你想再打钱德一顿吗？
Hey, you wanna hit Chandler again?
我必须要想办法
I'm just gonna deal with it.
我必须要离开这里！
I gotta get out of here!
我不管你们怎么看 她一定有心事
I don't care what you guys say,something's bothering her.
你知道吗，我想我当时是十六岁
You know,I think I was 16.
你知道，我想我根本不在乎
You know,I think I don't care.
求求你，只要剪后面一点点
Please,just a little bit off the back.
我还是坚持不要
I'm still on "no."
早安
Morning.
你们能不能闭上眼睛一秒钟？
Could you close your eyes for a sec?
不，不，不 我可不要再上当
No,no,no. I'm not falling for that again.
怎么回事？
What's going on?
昨晚我做了一件蠢事
I sort of did a stupid thing last night.
你做了什么蠢事？
What stupid thing did you do?
好了保罗，现在你见了大家，大家也都见了你了
Paolo, now you've seen everybody and they've all seen you.
怎么发生的？
How did this happen?
我昨晚凑巧碰到他
I kind of ran into him last night.
在哪里？ 在他的公寓
-Where? -At his apartment.
这是果汁吗？
Is this juice?
你忘了他勾引菲比 所以你才甩了他？
And the fact that you dumped him because he hit on Phoebe?
天啊，我真是可悲 我是个烂货！
Oh,God,I know. I'm pathetic,I'm a loser.
亲爱的，你不可悲 你只是伤心
Honey,you're not pathetic. You're just sad.
大家伤心时都会干蠢事
People do stupid things when they're upset.
如果每个我不该上床的人 都给我五毛钱…
My God,if I had a nickel for every guy I wish I hadn't
但这是关于你的大错误
But this is about your horrible mistake.
对不起，我们迟到了
Sorry we're late.
我们…
We were....
发生过接触
Well,there was touching.
嗨，罗斯
Hey,Ross!
真是…
What a....
你在这里干什么？
What are you doing here?
跟瑞秋做爱！
I do Raquel!
他回来了？
So he's back?
对，他回来了 有什么问题吗？
Yeah,he's back. Is that a problem?
没问题
No,not a problem.
很好，很高兴没有问题
Good. Glad it's not a problem.
你不能再碰我的屁股！
You're gonna have to not touch my ass.
尽管有美味的面包 与浓厚的紧张气氛…
Despite the yummy bagels and palpable tension...
我要去改裤子了
... my pants need to be altered.
你见到法兰基时 替我问个好
When you see Frankie,tell him Joey Tribbiani says hello.
他会明白我的意思
He'll know what it means.
你确定他能解得开密码吗？
You sure he'll crack that code?
上次保罗来这里时 我的头发要可爱多了
It's funny. The last time Paolo was here,my hair was so much cuter.
好吧
All right.
但你要保证不会挑剔与专横…
But you have to promise that you will not be all controlly and bossy...
不会像个莫妮卡
...and all Monica about it.
我保证
I promise.
好，让我看看
All right,let's see.
你们有一些会被剪掉 有些不会
Now,some of you are gonna get cut and some of you aren't.
但我保证绝对不会痛
But I promise,none of you will feel a thing.
我不干了 我什么都没说！
-That's it. I quit. -What? I didn't say anything!
但这不是一张信任的表情
But this isn't the face of a person who trusts a person.
这是一张，你知道的…
This is the face of a person who,you know...
不信任人的表情
...doesn't trust a person.
对不起，对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
这比我们说的要短了一点
It's just a little shorter than what we had discussed.
你放轻松好吗？ 我知道要怎么剪
Would you relax? I know what I am doing.
他的发型就是这样
This is how he wears it.
谁的发型就是这样？
How who wears it?
黛米摩儿（影星）
Demi Moore.
黛米摩儿不是一个“他”
Demi Moore is not a "he."
他在《阔公子》 与《十全十美》的电影中都是一个“他”
Well,he was a "he" in Arthur and in 10.
那是杜德利摩尔！
That's Dudley Moore!
我说我要像黛米摩儿！
I said I wanted it like Demi Moore!
喔，老天！
Oh,my God!
天啊！
Oh,God!
我的天，真对不起！
Oh,my God! I'm sorry!
黛米摩儿是哪一个？
Which one is Demi Moore?
她是女星！演过《叛逆性骚扰》《桃色交易》和《人鬼情未了》
She's the actress that was in Disclosure,Indecent Proposal,Ghost!
她的头发非常美！
She's got gorgeous hair.
我知道！
I know!
这就是为什么我想像她那样！
That's why i wanted to look like her.
-你知道的，我妈妈死了… -哦，上帝啊
-You know, my mom ' s d ead.-Oh, my God.
哦，我的屁股看起来像飞机一样
Well, this is what my butt must look like to a fly.
你的袖子要多长？
How long do you want the cuffs?
至少要跟裤子一样长的寿命
At least as long as I have the pants.
我听懂了
I just got that.
现在要量内缝
Now we'll do your inseam.
她的情况如何？
How is she?
现在还不知道
It's too soon to tell.
她在休息，这是好征兆
She's resting,which is a good sign.
头发怎么样？
How's the hair?
我不骗你 真的很不好看
I'm not gonna lie to you. It doesn't look good.
-你不能做点什么吗？ -此时此刻，最好是静静地等待
-There's nothing you can do?-At this point, it's a waiting game.
我在一边加上发夹 似乎能阻止卷曲
I put a clip on one side,which seems to have stopped the curling.
我们能不能看看她？
Can we see her?
你的头发太好看了 会让她伤心
Your hair looks too good. It'd upset her.
罗斯，你去看看她好了
Ross,you come on in.
你还好吗？
Well,how you doing?
我很好
I'm okay.
这么糟糕对吧？
That bad,huh?
我可以感觉到 女人难过脆弱的时候
Look,I can sense when women are depressed and vulnerable.
这是我的天赋之一
It's one of my gifts.
乔伊，当我看到他与她一起下飞机…
Joey,when I saw him get off that plane with her...
我以为我坠入了谷底
...I really thought I just hit rock bottom.
但今天是谷底…
But today,it's like there's rock bottom...
下面还有五十尺厚的垃圾…
... 50 feet of crap...
…然后就是我
...then me.
你必须告诉罗斯你的感受
Tell Ross how you feel.
我怎么能告诉他？ 茱莉呢？
Come on,how can I just tell him? What about Julie?
又怎么样？ 他们才在一起两周
What about her? They've only been going out for two weeks.
罗斯已经爱你十年了
Ross has been in love with you for 10 years.
我不知道，我不知道…
I don't know. I don't know.
我交往过很多女人
I've been with my share of women.
我交往过很多别人的女人
I've been with a lot of people's share of women.
但重点是…
But the point is...
我从来没有对任何人 像罗斯对你这样专情…
... I've never felt about anyone the way Ross felt about you.
真的吗？
Really?
喂，意大利同胞！
Yo,paesano!
我能跟你谈一下吗？
Can I talk to you for a sec?
你的裁缝…
Your tailor...
是个大坏蛋！
...is a very bad man!
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
怎么样？
Hey,what's going on?
乔伊的裁缝…
Joey's tailor...
占了我的便宜
...took advantage of me.
-什么？ -不可能！我去他那里十二年了
-What？-No way! I've been going to the guy for 1 2 years.
他说要量我的内缝
He said he was gonna do my inseam.
他的手沿着我的腿往上摸 然后就…
Then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite
什么？
What?
包住了
Cupping.
他们就是这样量裤子的！
That's how they do pants!
首先量一边 把小弟弟推到一旁
First they go up one side,they move it over.
然后量另一边 把小弟弟推回来，然后量后面
Then they go up the other side,move it back,then they do the rear.
罗斯，告诉他 裁缝量裤子不都是这样？
Ross,tell him. Isn't that how a tailor measures pants?
是的，的确是这样 在监狱里！
Yes,yes,it is. In prison!
你是怎么搞的？
What's the matter with you?
什么？
What?
不是这样？
That's not?
我的老天！
Oh,my God!
我要用一壶咖啡做掩护！
I 'll put on a pot of coffee.
就算是玛丽泰勒摩尔（七十年代的演员）也比这个要好
Even Mary Tyler Moore would've been better.
别这样，没那么糟，你不知道
Come on. It' s not that bad.You never know.
喇叭裤又开始流行了
Bell - bottoms came back.
我喜欢
I like it.
真的，我认为它“十全十美”（杜德利摩尔的电影）！
I do. I think it's a 10!
谢谢
Thank you.
我的头发很让人开怀
My hair is very amused.
事情还可能更糟
Come on,things could be worse.
你可能会被“困在纽约月光中” （《阔公子》的电影台词）
You could "get caught between the moon and New York City.
我知道很疯狂，不过千真万确 （《阔公子》的电影台词）
I know it's crazy,but it's true."
谢谢
Thank you.
我要走了，待会见
Well,I gotta go. Bye.
瑞秋，再见！
Bye,Rach!
慢着，你要走了？
Wait,are you leaving?
所以我才说再见
That's what I meant by "bye."
我能不能跟你说一下话？
Can I talk to you for a sec?
当医生检查疝气时…
When the doctor does that hernia test....
那样做就没有关系
That's okay.
如果你的修理工这么做的话
If your mechanic does it....
怎么啦？
What's going on?
首先…
Well,okay,first of all...
保罗与我没有在一起
... Paolo and I are not back together.
那是我干的一件蠢事
That was a stupid thing I did.
如果我能使时光倒转…
If I could go back in time and do it again...
我绝对不会这么做
...well,I wouldn't.
其次…
Second of all....
什么？
What?
我要先问清楚 这是不是当你与男友分手…
Is this one of those things where you break up with a guy...
我告诉你我的想法…
... I tell you what I think...
然后第二天你又重修旧好…
...and the next day you get back together with him...
我就变成一个大蠢蛋？
...and I look like a complete idiot?
好，我觉得他实在很烂
Well,then,I think the guy's scum.
我恨死他了 我真的很厌恶他
I hate him. I mean,I actually I physically hate him.
我一直很厌恶他
I always have.
你值得更好的男人喜欢你
And you are way too good to be with a guy like that.
真的？
Really?
你值得一个真正能欣赏你的人
You deserve to be with someone who appreciates you...
了解你有多么幽默…
...and who gets how funny...
多么温柔，多么体帖…
...and sweet and amazing...
多么美丽性感…
...and adorable and sexy you are.
每天早上醒来都会想着…
You know? Someone who wakes up every morning thinking:
天啊，我跟瑞秋在一起！
"Oh,my God. I'm with Rachel!"
这个人能让你感觉非常好
You know? Someone who makes you feel good.
就像我与茱莉一样
Like the way I do with Julie.
你还没说完“其次”
Was there a "second of all"?
不，我想这就是了
No,I think that was the whole "all."
我要走了
I gotta go.
谢谢
Thanks.
不，我向天发誓，爸！
No,I swear to God,Dad!
不是这样子量裤子的！
That's not how they measure pants!
我想要剪个短发 就像安迪麦克道威尔（《四个婚礼一个葬礼》的主演）的发型
I was thinking of doing it shorter,like Andie MacDowell's haircut.
这我会剪 真的？
-Yeah,I could do that. -Really?
你要现在就剪吗？ 太好了！
-You wanna do it now? -Great!
待会见
See you.
这次我要弄清楚
I just wanna make really sure this time.
安迪麦克道威尔就是演 《四个婚礼一个葬礼》的人吗？
Andie MacDowell is the girl from Four Weddings and a Funeral,right?
不是
No.
那是罗迪麦克道威尔（《人猿星球》的主演）
That's Roddy McDowall.
安迪麦克道威尔是演 《人猿星球》的那个家伙
Andie MacDowell is the guy from Planet of the Apes.
谢谢 别客气
-Thank you. -You're welcome.